radiologyassistant.nl 2019-07-31

# The Radiology Assistant : Privacy and cookie statement

We respect the privacy of visitors to www.radiologyassistant.nl and other relations. We ensure that the provided personal information is treated confidentially. Storage and processing of personal data is solely done in accordance with our services and compliant with the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

## Storage and processing of data

Storage and processing of your data is done in accordance with the intended use of our website, general terms and conditions, our security standards and the requirements set by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

These data are no longer held by us than is necessary for the following purposes and subsequently removed. No use is made of automated decision making and/or profiling. Data are stored exclusively by The Radiology Assistant in the EU and are not shared with third parties unless an imperative legal decision or law requires this.

## Purposes of storage and processing of data

General visitor data is only kept up to date for the provision of our services, the operation of the website and your user convenience. Any personal data you have left or is provided by you or is provided by us for management purposes, will only be stored and processed by us for the intended use, provision of our services and the therefore required management of the resulting relationships. GDPR basis: The implementation of the agreement.

## Use of cookies and scripts

When presenting information on www.radiologyassistant.nl, we solely use cookies and scripts that are necessary for the use of the website. A cookie is a simple small file that is sent along with pages from this website and stored by your browser on the hard disk of your computer. No personal data or data is used that personally identifies users. You can disable these cookies via your browser. Disabling these cookies may influence the usability and your experience of the website.

## Analysis & Statistics

At www.radiologyassistant.nl we strictly use server based statistic software. While using cookies and scripts no personal data that leads to personal identification is stored or processed. Acquired data for analytical purposes is not shared with third parties.

## YouTube

Within www.radiologyassistant.nl videos are offered by means of and via the external medium YouTube. Via the cookie settings in www. radiologyassistant.nl you can choose to view these videos. If you choose so and access / start a video, you will enter the YouTube platform. YouTube will use cookies and may collect personal data. By using this medium we assume that you are familiar with and agree with their privacy policy and your privacy settings there.

## Social media; Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter

At www.radiologyassistant.nl we can occasionally offer the possibility to share pages using external links to social media. When offered and using these external links, no data is held and/or shared by www.radiologyassistant.nl. By using the former external links you are entering the respective Social Media platforms which use cookies and scripts that (may) hold your data. By using these external services, we assume that you are familiar with and agree with their privacy policy and your privacy settings there.

## Customize your cookie settings

Click here to adjust your cookie settings.

Please pay attention to the following :  
If you adjust your settings from optimal to minimal, you should then:

• delete the cookies that were placed in your browser yourself.  
• Refresh your page (CTRL-F5)

## Your rights

If you have a direct relationship with The Radiology Assistant or you have left data on this website, The Radiology Assistant is solely responsible for the personal data that we may have from you. You can of course contact us to exercise your rights.

As data controller we are obliged to follow up on the exercise of your rights and to comply with your request within 1 month. If granting is complex and requires more time, we are obliged to respond with reasons and to respond to your request within 3 months. Unless a request is unfounded or excessive, you may not be charged for this.

**1\. The right to data portability** You can request to transfer your data in digital form to you or a third party.

**2\. The right to be 'forgotten'**

If your relationship with The Radiology Assistantis non-existent, expired or changed, your personal data may become redundant or obsolete for the original purposes but are kept by The Radiology Assistant for a statutory retention or for administrative, statistical or research purposes. If the aforementioned relation and / or purposes are unlawful, non-existent, expired or modified, you can request that your data will be deleted.

**3\. Right of access**

You have the right at any time to inspect the information that is stored.

**4\. Right to rectification and supplementation**

You can request to rectify or supplement your personal information that has been placed as information and that you believe to be unlawful, incomplete or incorrect for the stated purposes (foundations).

**5\. The right to limit the processing**

You can request to limit your personal data that has been placed as information and is in your view unlawful or superfluous for the stated purposes (foundations).

**6\. The right to object**

If the relationship in which your data is placed is not existing, expired or changed, your personal data may become redundant or obsolete for the original purposes but will be stored due to a statutory retention obligation or for administrative, statistical or research purposes. If the aforementioned relationship and / or objectives are unlawful, non-existent, expired or changed, you can lodge an objection and, for example, request that the processing be stopped and / or your data deleted.

**7\. The right to clear information**

You can request to provide insight into your personal data and for what purposes they are used.

**8\. The right to file a complaint**

As a data subject you have the right to file a complaint with your national Data Protection Authority. You can find the procedure to do so at their respective websites.

## Customization of this privacy and cookie statement

The Radiology Assistant reserves the right to change this privacy and cookie statement. Changes will be published on this page.
